Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005
  - All Library Staff Meeting "Creating the 21st Century Library", 8 Jan 2008; cuid1385; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Presidential Representitives on Transportation Panel, 31 Jan 2008; cuid1387; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Hidgon Class, 7 Feb 2008; cuid1388; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - The Reality Show 2006, 25 Sept 2006; cuid1389; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - NYDIS Clergical Summit, 1 Jun 2007; cuid1390; 4 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Town Hall Meeting, 16 Nov 2006; cuid1391; 3 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Kimmel Shoot, 15 Sep 2006; cuid1392; 3 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Downtown Show at Grey Art Gallery, undated; cuid1393; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Philanthropy Interviews, Nov 2006; cuid1394; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - How to Strengthen Communities to Solve Tough Societal Problems, 24 Jan 2006; cuid1395; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - James Hanley and Susana Piscitiello, undated; cuid1396; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Mock Solicitation Audit, 5 Apr 2007; cuid1397; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - The Next NY, 7 Dec 2001; cuid1398; 4 minidvs (Box 77)
  - The Next NY, 7 Dec 2001; cuid1399; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - MIAP Fall 2005 Speaker Series: A Mexican, 14 Oct 2005; cuid1400; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Kimmel Ribbon Cutting and Dinner Final Edit, 7 Jul 2003; cuid1401; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - NYU Show #2, undated; cuid1402; 1 videocassettes (digital betacam) (Box 77)
  - Conference on Our Design, 5 Jun 2004; cuid1403; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Clive Davis Department of Recorded Music: Year 1, 1 Jan 2004; cuid1404; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 77)
  - Global Public Health: Thomas Bornemann, 28 Feb 2008; cuid1405; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - New York University Ultraviolet Live 2008, 28 Feb 2008; cuid1406; 10 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Steinhardt Symphony at Skirball, 4 Mar 2008; cuid1407; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Steinhardt Symphony at Skirball, 4 Mar 2008; cuid1408; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 77)
  - Albert Gallatin Lecture: An Evening with James Schamus, 12 Mar 2008; cuid1409; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Global Public Health: Hidden Hunger, 27 Mar 2008; cuid1410; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - APA Food Series: Why are we Afraid of Food?, 27 Mar 2008; cuid1411; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Fales Food Series: The Power of the Pen, 13 Mar 2008; cuid1412; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - NYU's Media Talk Series, 25 Mar 2008; cuid1413; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Courant Oral History Project: Louis Nirenberg, 23 Feb 2007; cuid1414; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Human Resources, 13 Apr 2007; cuid1415; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Stern CFR Panel, 18 Nov 2008; cuid1416; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Fales Library: Dennis Cooper Reading and Panel, 3 Dec 2007; cuid1417; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - 2007 Albert Gallatin Lecture "Defending Rights Without Courts and Judges", 10 Dec 2007; cuid1418; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - The Invisible Cure: Africa, the West, and the Fight against AIDS", 4 Dec 2007; cuid1419; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Library Staff Meeting, 1 Jan 2008; cuid1420; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Central HR I-9 Training, 8 Jan 2008; cuid1421; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - MLK Celebration Week: Marquee Event, 24 Jan 2008; cuid1422; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - New York Institute of Philosophy: Ronald Dworkin, 13 Nov 2007; cuid1423; 3 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Keep a Child Alive: Student Aids Summit, 15 Nov 2008; cuid1424; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Keep a Child Alive: Student Aids Summit, 15 Nov 2008; cuid1425; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Discourses of Republicanism, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1426; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Jonathan Lear, 17 Nov 2008; cuid1427; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - NYU Wagner Reynolds Speaker Series, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1428; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS Yaddo: Conversations about America, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1429; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Discourses of Republicanism, 13 Nov 2008; cuid1430; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - The Global Burden of a Chronic Disease: A Rising Epidemic, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1431; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Global Financial Crisis and Future Impact, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1432; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Research Channel: John Jost Interview, 27 Oct 2008; cuid1433; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Research Channel: John Jost Interview, 27 Oct 2008; cuid1434; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Institute of Ancient World: Speaker Mario Savio, 12 Nov 2008; cuid1435; 3 minidvs (Box 78)
  - APA Dumpling & Dynasty: Morning Panels, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1436; 11 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Parents Day, 18 Oct 2008; cuid1437; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - CAS Memorial Service, 6 Sep 2008; cuid1438; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - CAS Memorial Service, 6 Sep 2008; cuid1439; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - MTA Ravitch Hearings Session 1 & 2, 15 Sep 2008; cuid1440; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Martha Wilson Documentation: Dilemmas, undated; cuid1441; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Fales Food Series, 18 Nov 2008; cuid1442; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Sword of Judith Conference, 18 Apr 2008; cuid1443; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - SARI Economics Interview, 2 Dec 2008; cuid1444; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Stern CFR Panel #3, 2 Dec 2008; cuid1445; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - American Cheeses by Clark Wolf at Fales, 3 Dec 2008; cuid1446; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - How Food and Food Writing have Changed, 20 Nov 2008; cuid1447; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS Yaddo: Hemmerding T. Haynes, 4 Dec 2008; cuid1448; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Filming Science (Secrecy), 19 Nov 2008; cuid1449; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Siemans Science Competition 2008, 7 Dec 2008; cuid1450; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - HR: HIPAA Training Videos at Benefits, 5 Dec 2008; cuid1451; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Global Public Health Event: Human Rights, 23 Jan 2009; cuid1452; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Economics DRI Conference, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1453; 4 videocassettes (dvcam)
  - CAS: Yaddo "Art and Social Conflict: Culture Wars from 1930 to the Present, 4 Feb 2009; cuid1454; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo "Art and Social Conflict: Culture Wars from 1930 to the Present, 4 Feb 2009; cuid1455; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - Donor Interviews: Tammiment Library, 11 Dec 2008; cuid1456; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - What Would the Poor Say: Debates in Aid, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1457; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Reynolds: Social Entrepreneurship Chuck D Series, 26 Jan 2009; cuid1458; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo: Off the Page, 21 Jan 20091; cuid1459; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - CAS: Yaddo: Off the Page, 21 Jan 2009; cuid1460; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - MLK Marquee Event, 22 Jan 2009; cuid1461; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Court Reform in China, 19 Feb 2009; cuid1462; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Gallatin Lecture: Jim Abramson, 10 Feb 2009; cuid1463; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Zuckerman Forum 2009 Sessions 1,2,3, 13 Feb 2009; cuid1464; 6 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - YNH Coming Up Slates, undated; cuid1465; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Program Office: Big fun Day, undated; cuid1466; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - University Wide Rooftop Shoot, undated; cuid1467; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Ahecha Move B-Roll, undated; cuid1468; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - Exterior Campus Reel, 6 Jun 2002; cuid1469; 1 minidvs (Box 80)
  - Staff Interview, 6 Jun 20021; cuid1470; 1 minidvs (Box 78)
  - John Sexton Martin Luther King Jr. Address, undated; cuid1471; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Recognizing and Responding to Students in Need, 23 Feb 2009; cuid1472; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - APA Presents Dana Tai Burgess & Co., 11 Mar 2009; cuid1473; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - APA Presents Dana Tai Burgess & Co., 11 Mar 2009; cuid1474; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - SCPS Podcast The U.S. Economy, 27 Jan 2009; cuid1475; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 78)
  - SCPS Podcast The U.S. Economy, 27 Jan 2009; cuid1476; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Stern: Sani Lecture, 9 Mar 2009; cuid1477; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - SHARP: Lecture Series: United States, 24 Nov 2008; cuid1478; 2 minidvs (Box 80)
  - Institute of Public Knowledge: Inernational Relations, 4 Mar 2009; cuid1479; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - Restored Financial Stability, 6 Mar 2009; cuid1480; 11 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - UVL 2009, 26 Feb 2009; cuid1481; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NYMTC Meeting, 19 Mar 2009; cuid1482; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NCDP Session 3: Afternoon Sessions, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1483; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - New Multilateralism: Gordon M. Brown, 25 Mar 2009; cuid1484; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Fales: Food and Celebration: A Long History, 5 Mar 2009; cuid1485; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Tamiment Conference: Academic Freedom, 3 Apr 2009; cuid1486; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Wagner: Michael Bllomberg and Non-Profits, 6 Apr 2009; cuid1487; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NYU Alumni and Friends, 23 Mar 2009; cuid1488; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Courant: Jack Schwartz Memorial, 26 Mar 2009; cuid1489; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 6 Apr 2009; cuid1490; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - GPH: Health in Africa, 16 Apr 2009; cuid1491; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Courant Spring Lecture, 23 Mar 2009; cuid1492; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - NYU Stern "Torch Club Lunch", 17 Apr 2009; cuid1493; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NYU Stern "Torch Club Lunch", 17 Apr 2009; cuid1494; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - The 2009 Zuckerman Forum, 21 Apr 2009; cuid1495; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - Fales Library: Annual Fales Lecture, 14 Apr 2009; cuid1496; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - SCPS: Media Talk with David Carr and Tina Brown, 25 Feb 2009; cuid1497; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Scholars and Artists: George Stoney, 29 Apri 2009; cuid1498; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Aramark: Opera Performance, 26 Apr 2009; cuid1499; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Wagner: Reynolds Social Entrepreneurial, 30 Apr 2009; cuid1500; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - Obama's 100 Days, 24 Apr 2009; cuid1501; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - National Public Policy Forum, 18 Apr 2009; cuid1502; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Progress Review and Report, 13 Mar 2009; cuid1503; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Shared Care Integrated, 13 Mar 2009; cuid1504; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Depression Identification, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1505; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NCDP 2009: Period 3 and Beyond, 14 Mar 2009; cuid1506; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - NYMTC Meeting: A Shared Vision for a Sustainable Region, 19 Mar 2009; cuid1507; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 79)
  - SCPS: Ninth Annual Cal Ramsey, 19 Feb 2009; cuid1508; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 79)
  - CAS: From Slavery to Freedom, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1509; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Scholars and Artists, 30 Sep 2008; cuid1510; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Coles Science Salon, 1 Oct 2008; cuid1511; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 80)
  - Compassionate Leadership, 24 Sep 2008; cuid1512; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - CAS From Slavery to Freedom, 26 Sep 2009; cuid1513; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - What's Next? The Global Financial Crisis, 20 Oct 2008; cuid1514; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - SCPS Media Talk: Arthur Miller, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1515; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - SCPS Media Talk: Crossing the Line, 21 Oct 2008; cuid1516; 2 minidvs (Box 80)
  - Emerging and Disappering Immigrant, 16 Oct 2008; cuid1517; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Global Public Health: Rethinking HIV, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1518; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - President of Albania, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1519; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Conscious Capitalism, 8 Oct 2008; cuid1520; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - New Israel Fund, undated; cuid1521; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 80)
  - Rudin CTR: Making the Connection, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1522; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Moving the Needle: Improving Collaboration, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1523; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Depression Treatment, 25 Oct 2009; cuid1524; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - Stern CFR Panel #1, 11 Nov 2008; cuid1525; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - King David Gala, 14 Nov 2008; cuid1526; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 80)
  - SCPS Podcast: The Emergency Economic, 29 Oct 2008; cuid1527; 0 dvd-r disks (Box 80)
  - Compassionate Leadership Powerpoint, 24 Sep 2008; cuid1528; 0 electronic discs (cd-rom) (Box 80)
  - Rudin Conference "Closing the Gap", 4 Jun 2014; cuid1529; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - NCRW National Council for Research on Women, 6 Jun 2006; cuid1530; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Steinhardt Reading Recovery, 4 Jun 2008; cuid1531; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 81)
  - SMPTE-NY Meeting "File Exchange", 4 Jun 2008; cuid1532; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - National Presidential Caucus: 2012 Primary, 24 Jun 2008; cuid1533; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 20 Jun 2008; cuid1534; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 20 Jun 2008; cuid1535; 16 minidvs (Box 81)
  - National College Depression Conference, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1536; 20 dvd-r disks (Box 81)
  - Metro Center TACD: Summer Institute, 9 Jul 2008; cuid1537; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Metro Center TACD: Summer Institute Day Two, 10 Jul 2008; cuid1538; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Keynote, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1539; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 1 "Rewriting the Bible", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1540; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 2 "The Dead Sea Sect", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1541; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 3 "The Scrolls and Second Temple Judaism", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1542; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 4 "Judean Desert Texts", 6 Mar 2008; cuid1543; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Public Affairs Spotlight Shoot: Raw Footage, Penny Halkitis, Ann Morning, and Rough Cut, 23 Aug 2005; cuid1544; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 81)
  - Neil Postman: Raw Footage and Select Segments, undated; cuid1545; 3 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: LGBT Issues, undated; cuid1546; 4 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Washington Square News, undated; cuid1547; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: WNYU, undated; cuid1548; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Career Services, undated; cuid1549; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - OISS, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1550; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - OISS 1: American Idioms Seminar, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1551; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - OISS 2: Mixed Drinks American, 5 Apr 2002; cuid1552; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Interview with University Archivist Nancy Cricco, undated; cuid1553; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Clinton on Campus: Registration Campaign, 24 Apr 2002; cuid1554; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Conversations with Jie Tao, 15 Oct 1997; cuid1555; 1 sound cassettes (dat) (Box 81)
  - New York University in London, 28 Nov 2001; cuid1556; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Campus Flash: Fall 2002, 1 Oct 2002; cuid1557; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - Dogeaters: From Novel to the Stage, 30 Jan 2001; cuid1558; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: Skirball, 21 Aug 2008; cuid1559; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: WaMu, 25 Aug 2008; cuid1560; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Reality Show 2008: WaMu, 25 Aug 2008; cuid1561; 8 dvd-r disks (Box 81)
  - NYU Portraits, 29 Sept 2008; cuid1562; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Simon Peres, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1563; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Martha Graham Panels, 18 Sep 2008; cuid1564; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Fales A.I.R. Gallery, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1565; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Financial Access Initiative: Program Feed, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1566; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - Wagner Financial Access Initiative Event, 16 Sep 2008; cuid1567; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - A Discussion with UK Foreign Secretary, 25 Sep 2008; cuid1568; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Key Learning and Summary of Day 1, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1569; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Strategies for Sustaining, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1570; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Self Managment Team, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1571; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Progress Review, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1572; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Depression Care Workflow, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1573; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Primary Care Benefit, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1574; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Understanding the Importance, 24 Oct 2008; cuid1575; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NCDC: Advanced Self Management, 25 Oct 2008; cuid1576; 1 minidvs (Box 81)
  - NYU Portraits, 29 Sep 2008; cuid1577; 2 minidvs (Box 81)
  - 50th Anniversary of Brown vs. Board of Education lecture/panel, 17 May 2004; cuid1578; 3 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 79)
    Barcode: 31142042272966
  - Stern Barcelona 2009: Global Alumni, 12 Jun 2009; cuid1579; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - SCPS: McGhee "Online Interviews", 21 Jan 2009; cuid1580; 7 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies (CAS): Writing, 24 Apr 2009; cuid1581; 13 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Congressional Oversight Hearing, 28 May 2009; cuid1582; 3 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Fales Food Series: "NY Farm Connections", 4 Apr 2009; cuid1583; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Bankruptcy and the Financial Crisis, 30 Jun 2009; cuid1584; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Reading Recovery Program Graduation, 5 Jun 2009; cuid1585; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Reality Show, 26 Aug 2009; cuid1586; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - NYU Portraits: Voices of a People, 26 Aug 2009; cuid1587; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - College of Arts and Science Deans Lecture, 17 Sep 2009; cuid1588; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - President's Welcome and Reality Show, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1589; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - President's Welcome and Reality Show, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1590; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1591; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Constitution Day, 14 Sep 2009; cuid1592; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies: Legitimating Violence Execution, Human Sacrifice, Assassination, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1593; 14 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Center for Ancient Studies: Legitimating Violence Execution, Human Sacrifice, Assassination, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1594; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Development Research Institute (DRI): What Would the Poor Say? Debateds in Aid Evaluations, 6 Feb 2009; cuid1595; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - The Children of Buroughs: New York Archives, 8 Oct 2009; cuid1596; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - The Unbearables, 24 Sep 2009; cuid1597; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Drug-Resistant TB and HIV/AIDS in Southern Africa: Human Rights, Evidence, and the Public Good, 8 Oct 2009; cuid1598; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 29 Jun 2009; cuid1599; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Churchill School Graduation, 29 Jun 2009; cuid1600; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Steinhardt TACD Workshop Marco Center, 29 Sep 2009; cuid1601; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Steinhardt TACD Workshop Marco Center, 29 Sep 2009; cuid1602; 4 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Music and Performing Arts Professions: Meeting on Disproportionality in Special Education, 9 Cct 2009; cuid1603; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Student Health Center: H1N1 Forum, 14 Oct 2009; cuid1604; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Creative Writing Program: Dance Program, 14 Dec 2008; cuid1605; 3 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Alumni Weekend: Happy Hour and Raffle, 3 Oct 2009; cuid1606; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Billy Collins Reading, 1 Sep 2009; cuid1607; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - CAS Freshman Convocation, 31 Aug 2009; cuid1608; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow Simulcast, 17 Oct 2009; cuid1609; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - CAS Parent's Day Video Overflow Simulcast, 17 Oct 2009; cuid1610; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Nursing Workshop, 1 Sep 2009; cuid1611; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 86)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Seth Goldman President and TeaEO of Honest Tea, 19 Oct 2009; cuid1612; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Remarque Lecture: Tony Judt, 19 Oct 2009; cuid1613; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - E.L. Doctorow Reader from "Homer and Langley", 22 Oct 2009; cuid1614; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 86)
  - Everything You Wanted to Know (and Didn't) About Film Festivals, 3 Nov 2009; cuid1615; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Julie Shifman Presentationa at NYU, 9 Nov 2009; cuid1616; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 87)
  - Julie Shifman Presentationa at NYU, 9 Nov 2009; cuid1617; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Peter Orszag, 3 Nov 2009; cuid1618; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Annual Leon Levy Lecture, 5 Nov 2009; cuid1619; 2 minidvs (Box 87)
  - Medical Education Matters: A Theory Building Conference, 11 Nov 2009; cuid1620; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy: Philip Kitcher, 16 Nov 2009; cuid1621; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Courant Institute Alumni Presentation, 13 Nov 2009; cuid1622; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - MLK Keynote Event: Howard Zinn, 21 Jan 2010; cuid1623; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - "You are Cordially Invited": the Art and Influence of Robert Blanchon, 2010 Jan 26; cuid1624; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Columbian Consulate Webcasts, 2010 Aug 8; cuid1625; 5 dvd-r disks (Box 87)
  - NYU Schack Institute of Real Estate Press, 2010 Jan 10; cuid1626; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - National College Depression Partnership, 2000 Jan 15; cuid1627; 24 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - 11th Annual Irving H. Jurow Lecture, 2010 Feb 2; cuid1628; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Fales Food Series: Italian Food in New York, 2010 Feb 3; cuid1629; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - David Wonjnarowicz Photographer, 2010 Feb 4; cuid1630; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 87)
  - Humanities: Thinking Through Violence, 2010 Feb 9; cuid1631; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Karl Hoffman, 2010 Feb 16; cuid1632; 2 minidvs (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Karl Hoffman, 2010 Feb 16; cuid1633; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 88)
  - Will Wright, 2010 Feb 17; cuid1634; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - SCPS Schack Online Interviews, 2010 Jan 21; cuid1635; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - CGA Public Events Series, 2010 Feb 17; cuid1636; 1 minidvs (Box 88)
  - SCPS Podcast: Bjorn Hanson, 2010 Feb 22; cuid1637; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Schack Panel "Real Estate: A Local Business", 2010 Feb 23; cuid1638; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Chris Jordan, 2010 Feb 23; cuid1639; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Ultraviolet Live, 2010 Feb 25; cuid1640; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Google versus Apple: Who Will Win?, 2010 Mar 2; cuid1641; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Mabou Mines Opening Night Reception, 2010 Mar 4; cuid1642; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 88)
  - Remappings: Asia/Pacific/America, 2010 Mar 5; cuid1643; 12 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)
  - Steinhardt Symphony Orchestra, 2010 Mar 8; cuid1644; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 88)